Super ingots. Okay. Can we make a
pickaxe? Oh, okay. How good can it be?
This is Minecraft, but I can craft super
items. How this works is that there's
brand new super ores in caves, and once
mined, we can craft super sword, super
armor, and even super that thing. What
even is that thing? So, what does a
super item even do? And how hard are
they to craft? Stay tuned to find out.
All right, let's begin. Where if you
look at the top right, we just got every
single super item in Minecraft. And when
I say super, these things break
Minecraft. Where if you saw the intro,
you probably got a good sneak peek of
them. But let me show you guys what I
mean. Because with this crafting book,
these right here are the super items. We
have the rainbow sword, the chest plate
with the elytra, the rainbow dragon egg,
which is our goal, even the super bread.
I'm hiding the enchantments for now, but
just know later on it is insane. Our
first item though, the super pickaxe.
Guys, this thing is crazy. We're hiding
the enchantments until we get it. But
just read when in hand plus 10,0001
mining efficiency. That's the craft
right there. So, in the meantime, we get
the wooden pickaxe. Yes. Mine, mine,
mine, mine, mine. Now, stone pickaxe. In
the meantime, we're going to be doing
the normal Minecraft stuff, which is
getting some food, making the bread,
talking to the villager.
>> Please stop me. I'm looking for the
space station.
>> Uh, nice. Oh, wait, guys. That's the
first super ore right there. Okay, I
need an iron get. Where is the iron
golem? Found you.
Thank you, sir. And now with this, we
can go to make the iron pickaxe. This is
the comp before the storm. Oh, and look
at that. The rainbow ingots. Very cool
animation. Shout out to admins. Now we
mine this. And that's going to be three
super ingots from one. You already know
what time it is. Crafting table. We can
only make one thing on here, and that's
the super pickaxe. You guys won't see it
just yet, but now with this craft done,
ladies and gentlemen, look at this.
Efficiency 1 billion, unbreaking 1
billion, and fortune 1 billion. The
super pickaxe. This thing feels too
powerful. So, what happens if I mine? It
does fortune on anything. No way. Yo,
wait. What are you doing here?
>> Oh, thank you. Does it work with gravel?
Oh my gosh. Wait, that's crazy. If it
works with everything. Oh, what about
this? Oh my goodness. Ladies and
gentlemen, unlimited bread, unlimited
bells, torches for days. What about
sheep? Oh, this thing does no damage.
Dang. It does not work on the sheep.
Sorry. Unlimited sugarcane. I guess I do
need some wood. So, we might as well do
this real quick. That's crazy. Holy,
does it work on apples. Uh, sooner or
later, maybe it drops. Oh, maybe it
does. Wait, even unlimited coal. I don't
think we need that much coal, but it's
nice. Oh gosh. Okay, on to the next
super item. We did the pickaxe. Next up,
let's do super bread, the enchantments,
unbreaking 1 billion, mending 1 billion,
and everlasting 1 billion. What does
that even mean? We need eight rainbow
ingots. Does the pickaxe work with the
rainbow ingots? Who knows? Wait, what if
I dig straight down? Guys, this is a
terrible idea. What am I doing? I can't
see. This is crazy. Oh, wait. We found
something. What is grass doing down
here? Um, what is this? Digging straight
down yet again. Come on. I need my super
ingots. What if I dig straight that way
or this way? Oh, wait. I hear something.
Oh, a cave. Nice. Don't have a super
sword yet, but sooner or later,
hopefully it's pretty good. Oh, and we
got some iron. Exactly. Stacks of iron.
All right, mission for right now. Get
more super ingots and figure out what
the bread is. Also, we got some lapis. I
only need to mine one of everything. Can
I mine this? Nope. What the bat doing?
He He's just stuck. Oh, never mind. All
right. If I was a super ingot, where
would I be? The other one was pretty
easy to find. I think it's anywhere in
the cave. Holy. Yeah. Okay. Well, we
found a lot of it. We have super ingot
there. Super ingot there. Oh, it even
diamonds. We don't need diamonds today.
We got the better version. Okay. Now,
the question is, do we just got to mine
one super ingot and then have unlimited
of it, or does Fortune not work with it?
Let's see. Um, okay. Okay, let me
actually go around it and hopefully it
works. Oh, wait. It might a good bit.
Only six of it. Oh, so it doesn't work
with the super ingot. Interesting. We
have 16 in total now, though. You
already know what time it is. One
grabbing table, one piece of bread, and
now our next item number two is going to
be the super bread. What is this thing
going to be? Okay. Um, can I eat it? Oh,
no, I can't. I need to take some fall
damage, I guess. Right here. Okay. Yep,
that works. Now, let's fight these guys.
Come on, take my hunger. Oh, and there
we go. Yeah, we're hungry now. All
right, what does this do? Wait, it
regens me and it's unlimited. World
hunger solved. This thing is amazing.
Okay, we don't need all this right here
or this. Okay, so now with the bread,
that is two super items out of 10. So,
we got to keep going down here. I would
like some armor suit cuz if we do die,
we got to restart. That's some super
ingots right by the creepers. Guys, I
don't think we can make the sword just
yet. That needs a blaze rod. Next thing
on the list, let's make the super
helmet. Oh, wait. I might need that guy.
By the way, if you guys can count how
many times I say super this video, big
props to you. Okay, let's actually get
to this next ore right here. I think
this should be 16. Oh, 13 right there.
And 19 super ingots. That's crazy. Okay,
so really what I need right now is
redstone, which is by the creepers.
Okay, this doesn't look like a good
idea. Smart idea is to find something
else. Let's go. Okay. Okay, we're going.
We're going to grab the red stone and
we're going to run. Oh gosh. Okay. Nope.
Nope. Nope. I got the red stone. We're
good. Let's get out of here and make the
helmet. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. I got to go
deeper. Not my best idea, but I got the
redstone. Nice. Why does this look fake?
All right, now the five ingots, one
redstone. Oh, and there it is. Super
helmet. Guys, listen to this list real
quick. Protection 1 billion. Blast
protection 1 billion. Fire protection,
projectile protection, thorns,
unbreaking 1 billion. It even says when
worn, negative, 1500% burn time. What
does that even mean? All right, let's
put it on. Cool. Wait, we got a new key.
Look at that on the screen. If I press
four. Yo, we got X-ray. This is so
broken. So, what we can literally do is
just mine straight to the super right
here. And we've made the mod to a bee. I
am at three out of 10 items. Next one.
We did the helmet. We did the pickaxe.
The bread. Leggings requires soul sand.
Chest plate requires wither skull. Oh
gosh. Super boots. I need a uncraftable
potion. I don't know how to get that.
Maybe it's any potion. The bow requires
blaze rods. And even the sword. New goal
on the piece of paper. Get to the
Nether. So, real quick, let's begin to
cook. Wait, low key, if this drops iron,
and if I break it with a pickaxe, am I
going to get a lot of iron? 24 iron
ingots. Now, moment of truth. Now to
see. Wait, did it multiply? No, we just
have a lot of furnaces. Well, on the
bright side, we now have a bucket. But I
do want to test one more thing. If I
make a chest and I put down the chest
and let's say we put one ironing inside.
Now, when I break the chest with the
pickaxe, does it multiply like this?
Nope. All right, we got to get to the
Nether. Let's go over here. And the good
thing about this pickaxe is all we got
to do is mine one obsidian. Like that.
That was so quick. Look at this. That's
crazy. We might need that, too. Oh my
gosh. We definitely need that. Okay, one
mine. Ladies and gentlemen, unlimited
diamonds. I think I just need some flint
for the flint and steel. Oh, wait. These
guys. Okay. Wait, what? There's no
chest. What is this?
>> Why do I feel scammed? We can make our
own chest. One chest there. One chest
there. Couple diamonds there. Couple
diamonds there. And now we'll walk back
inside. What? All right, we got the
gravel. Oh my gosh. Okay. Wait, that was
crazy right away. All the flint we'll
ever need. We just break that. There we
go. And if I break the fire with the
super pickaxe, nothing happens. Okay.
All right, ladies and gentlemen, it is
time. Let's go ahead and make one portal
like this. Okay. I don't think there's
really anything else we got to get. I
think we should be good here. So, with
the power of editing, 3 2 1. Nice. And
we're in. Okay. I don't need that guy
just yet. What I do need is one fortress
and a bunch of blazes. I want to make
the super sword next, which requires one
blaze rod. All right, we got the
fortress. Now for one of these guys. All
right, I just need one blaze rod. One,
two. Come on. Nope, not from him. Not
from him either. Any second now. Blazes,
please. All right, come on. Round two.
Yes. All right, run away. Run away. Run
away, guys. I think we can finally make
it. One blaze rod, two super ingots. Oh,
and there it is. Super sword. Here are
the enchantments, sharpness, smite, bait
of octopods, knockback, unbreaking,
looting. All at level 1 billion. Is this
going to one hit everything? All right,
let's test it out. Oh, what? No loot. No
loot again, huh? One hit. Oh, we're so
OP. Okay. Um, we don't need that
anymore. Two stacks of blaze rods. We
are now at four items. There are six
left to go. Reminder, this is the goal
right there. But the next one, we can
already go ahead and make the super bow.
Power flame punch unbreaking infinity.
All 1 billion. I got to do this in a
battle royale. Okay, it looks pretty
cool. What does it do when I shoot? Oh,
I just got so overwhelmed. That That's
crazy. Let's try over here. Holy cow.
Wait, that's crazy. Right. Okay. Also,
we have rainbow ore over here. Is it the
same one? Yep, it's the same one.
Incredible. It is so easy to get super
ingots, ladies and gentlemen. We might
one hit the dragon with this. What the
heck is that? Oh, I hit something. Shot
them. Next item. I think it might be
time we get some leggings. This time, we
only need one soul soil. Okay, we found
the soul soil, but let me test out the
bow real quick with these guys. Holy,
that's crazy. We're going to defeat the
dragon in a second. And we also found
some more super ingots. Nice. They're
all gone. How's it going, buddy? Let's
real quick get all the way here, grab
our pickaxe, and then just mine with one
of these guys. And now we have all the
soul so we ever need. All right, don't
mind me. Let's go all the way back up
and shoot one shot right there. Shot
him. And now on to the next super item.
We are making the ultimate suit of armor
right now, which with the soul soil, we
get super leggings. All right, I'm dying
over here. One second. Oh, that's so
broken. Oh no. Anyways, protection,
blast protection, fire protection,
projectile protection, swift sneak,
thorns, unbreaking 1 billion with some
crazy stats. Oh, look at me go. Why do I
feel like Minecraft caps it? It doesn't
feel like a billion, but it feels pretty
fast. Next craft. We are now over
halfway done with all these. Next up, we
have the boots, which requires a potion,
looks like, and a super chest plate,
which needs a wither skeleton skull.
Luckily, we have this sword. Oh, also
knender would be nice. All right, let's
go for the skull. Okay, I just need one
skeleton, most likely. Oh, wait. I think
that might be one. Two. Holy cow. Okay,
I don't think that's a skull. Yes, we
got the skull. With only two skeletons,
we now have 64 wither skeleton skulls.
Wait, are you guys thinking what I'm
thinking? Maybe very soon. Okay, before
we do anything crazy, let's go ahead and
make the chest plate. And with this, oh,
wait, that's the wrong thing. Let's go
and make the chest plate. And with this,
we get the super chest plate with, of
course, the crazy stats. But the most
important part about it is that now with
this on, we can fly. Oh, wait. What is
that? Let me real quick go here. Okay.
Does it let me like fly forever? Oh,
okay. It has like a little trail. Nice,
guys. We got a new key on the screen.
So, I think if I jump and then press
that. Oh, wait. That's sick. We can fly
forever. Yo. Okay, now we just need some
nether wart. I think I got to go this
way. Oh, we got some nether wart. And
because this is pretty much Minecraft,
every drop is multiplied. Let's get all
the nether wart in the game. Beautiful.
All we need now is just the potion which
we can go back for. And I also want to
see what a super eye of ender is. Three
items remain. Any enderman? Those are
not endermanmen. I am looking for one
enderman. What type of warp force is
this? It's the smallest warp forest
ever. Guys, the warp forest is there,
there, and there. And then it's done.
That's crazy. Oh well, we did find an
enderman. All right. Is this going to
one hit? Yo, guys. We now have all the
ender pulls we ever need. And all I need
to do is do one blaze powder, one end of
pearl, and now we have an eye of ender.
We're not done there yet, though,
because this is going to be super item
number eight out of 10, which will be
eight super ingots and one eye of ender
in the middle. And now we have the super
eye of ender. What is everlasting 1
billion? What does that even mean? Is
this just going to be infinite? Oh, I
can't use it here, right? I think it
might be time we go back with the power
of editing. 3 2 1. Ladies and gentlemen,
it is so good to be back. We got village
one, village two. Vote now. Which one
stays? Village one. Goodbye. Anyways,
guys, what do you guys think about the
fit so far?
>> Also, we keep trying to talk to us.
We're just in game characters that don't
actually speak language.
>> So, is it good?
>> That's all right.
>> Thank you. Wait, I got to test this. Oh,
that's crazy. We got all the iron we'll
ever need. Okay, before we throw the eye
avenger, what we really need right now
is going to be that sand right there.
Let's go all the way here. One, two,
three. I could use the pickaxe, but that
might be too much. Wait, I'm zooming
over here real quick. I have an idea.
Technically, could I just do this? Nope,
never mind. Okay, one furnace, some
sand, then we put in the coal. That's
all I need right there. Then, of course,
we make one brewing stand. Let's put
that right there. Go ahead and put the
blaze powder, some nether wart, and
while we wait, what can we do? Potatoes
for days. Did he pick all those up? Oh,
okay. We got the glass. All right. Now,
we just make the glass bottles. I only
need one potion, so technically we'll
just do that. Put that there. Okay,
we'll put that in right there. And while
we wait, let's see. Can I hit that pig
right there? One sec. Is that going to
hit? No. Oh, I have another pig piglin.
Okay, awkward potion. Ladies and
gentlemen, we have the super ingots, one
awkward potion, and now we can make
super boots. Going to get some
enchantments.
Yeah, you guys are right. Have the
falling, too. No, it's pretty much
everything 1 billion. And now with this,
we are fully super armor. Oh, I got
speed three. Yo, I also am burning down
that tree. My bad. Okay, before we use
the super eyeender, I think there's only
one other craft we got to get now. the
super dragon egg, which requires eight
super ingots. We have more than enough.
And one dragon egg. And before we use
this guy to go ahead and fight the
dragon, I have one fight I do want to
make. You see these guys right there? I
didn't get soul sand. One sec, guys. I
have two things to show you. First, we
got the soul sand. We just mine that.
Amazing. Now, let me show you guys what
happens when I crouch on the soul sand.
This is crazy. I did not realize the
super armor was like this. So,
obviously, we have swift sneak 1
billion. Let me show you guys how that
works on soul sand. Oh, that's crazy.
I need to find a soul biome right now.
Please hold. We will find one and crouch
immediately. Also, the speed of this
thing insane. While we look for the soul
biome, might as well mention right now.
And thank you so much to everyone that's
watched this far into the video. It is
always very appreciated. And as always,
if you guys want me to do a video idea
you guys have an idea about, feel free
to leave it in the comments down below.
How did I get that already? Guys, this
is it. Oh gosh. All right, we got the
super pants. Now we crouch. Yo, we're so
fast. That's crazy. I'm zooming. Yo, I'm
buddy hopping. Watch me. Watch this.
Oh. Wa. Yo, this movement is crazy. Oh
gosh. Okay, let's not fall in lava. Oh,
it's all good. We're pretty much
immortal to lava. Wow. All right, let's
do a bow fight. Shot him. Anyways, back
to the village. All right, we are back.
Now for the moment of truth. Before we
use the eye of, let's go ahead and fight
another boss, which is the wither. All
right. Wait, what? Huh? I'm so confused.
What's going on? Did the admins turn off
bosses or something? 1 2 3. What is
going on? Soul sand. Am am I supposed to
use soul soil? That's not right. I'm
very sure this is not right. One, two,
three. What? Since one, guys, please
explain to me in the comments. I am so
confused. All right, anyways. Uh, we got
the super bow and the super sword. I'm
going to guess maybe one hit. If it's
not one hit, there's caps in vanilla
Minecraft. Oh gosh. Wait, that did so
much damage. Huh, guys? I feel like the
armor's a lie. Oh. Oh. Oh, I one hit the
wither. Oh,
what did I just do? Strike a villager
with lightning. Sorry, buddy. Huh? Well,
that happened. Now, of course, we should
probably go to the stronghold now. That
would be the right idea, right? Ultimate
boss fight. I can outrun them. Let's go.
All right, let's see if I can fight them
with a sword. Oh, one hit. One hit. One
hit. All right, I'm not done. Last one.
I am the most OP I have been in a long
time. Well, one stack of Death Stars.
Don't worry, guys. The village is saved
and on fire. Anyways, time for the
surprise vendor. I throw this. Uh, wait.
How do I throw it? Oh, wait. It just
tped me to the stronghold. What? It's so
broken. All right. Um, well, let's just
break those guys now. We just put them
into the portal, which of course it
doesn't run out. And that really worked
like that. Is this a normal stronghold?
Yep, it's a normal stronghold with, of
course, the diamond horse arbor. Just
what we needed. Okay, final reminder,
guys. After we defeat the dragon, we got
to make the super dragon egg. We have
all the rainbow ingots and 64 Nether
stars. This is me at 9 out of 10 super
items. Holy cow. Well, um, I guess we
will now go one at the dragon. Let's do
this. Oh gosh, we are in. Okay. Oh,
wait. Look at my bridging. This is
crazy. Swift is amazing. All right,
let's get to it. Ender Dragon's right
there. And low key, if I just shoot one
arrow, I feel like it's going to die.
For now, let's break the crystals.
There's only one way to do this. Got
one. Got two. This is just outrageous.
We're going to break every end crystal
thing and probably kill the dragon along
the way. We're already hitting the
dragon. All right, last one. Oh, wait.
No, that's the last one right there.
That is all the crystals gone. Now, how
do we defeat the dragon? Uh, we have a
super sword, super bow. I guess maybe we
can try just uh shooting one arrow at
it. This is probably going to kill the
dragon egg.
Wow. Shot him. Down goes a dragon. Just
like that with one single hit. Now we
need the dragon egg to see what it
causes. I'm going to guess right now the
admin's going to make me fight 1,000
dragons. If not, then that's a dub. All
right, let's break that real quick. Oh,
wo. Wait, that's crazy. Hold up. If I
just do this. Oh,
that washed me off. Wait, wait, wait. So
before we get to that dragon egg, I have
made a cannon of travel. So if I just do
this. Okay. Run, jump. Yo, let me do
that again. Run, jump. I love this.
Maybe we use gravity tables instead.
Yeah, that's a good idea. Now we break
it with our pickaxe. One stack of
torches. Just what we needed. Oh no.
Wait. Okay, I thought I broke it for a
second. Okay, let's just do this slowly.
Oh gosh. Maybe not the best spot. It's
all good. We'll figure it out. Now we
break that. Okay, how am I supposed to
find it? Oh wait, it's despawning. Okay,
come on. One dragon egg. Please hold
this. Might take a second. Yes. Dragon
egg unlocked. All right. Can't forget
the XP. Now, one dragon egg surrounded
by the super ingots. And this should be
the final item. The super dragon egg. Am
I going to get my own dragon? Are we
going to spawn 1,000 dragons? What's
this going to do? Maybe I should use it
in the overworld. Yeah, let's do that.
Minecraft. Wait. I feel bad for that
village. We're going to go back. It's
cannon time.
Oh, that's crazy. What if I just use
one? Yo, new movement unlocked. You just
get on this guy with your super armor
and you just jump around. Nice. All
right. Now, in the middle of this
village. Oh, wait. These guys suck. Now,
in the middle of this village, we have
the super dragon egg. So, do I just like
right click it? Oh, wo. Okay. Wait, that
looks cool. What's going on? Dragon egg
is spinning up. As you guys can see, we
lived happily ever after. And so, with
that being done, hope you guys all
enjoyed. Thank you so much for watching
Minecraft, but with super items. This is
going to be the end of the video. So, if
you guys want to watch another video
just like this one, click the video on
the left. Or if you guys want to
subscribe to the channel or check out
our movie channel with the long video
compilations of old videos, those two
will be on the right. Anyways, we never
died. Right. Right.